Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are going to
learn the work of replace. Now this is the
effective work concept. It is a little
difficult to understand because it is a
concept of European languages.
Meaning, for example, in English,
let's introduce Mike Salier or he
introduces himself to Jaglal. So, in this, my self,
himself, etc.
can affect your pronunciation and these
come with the muhurta. They are scientifically
pronounced only that. Now, I am
learning Italian and Spanish today itself. There are a
lot of these in Spanish too.
In Spanish, they only end with -s, in Italian, they
end with -s, okay, so in German
and that, they are less in English only.
Unfortunately, first of all, it is
less in our Indian languages. So, to
understand this concept a little, this is
New Delhi Hall, but that is why I will
learn it by making it easy. So, first of all, you have to
reflect the inflected words.
In this, the doer and the object are
subject and  The object is related
or the same, so as I said that I
introduce Mike Shell or in such cases
but trust me, it is special in German, in its
condition, subsidy heart condition, we will
talk about it later, then you will come to know, so for this
I will tell you a concept that
you will have to remember a little bit, so let's divide it into two
parts, first of all, whatever we
saw in English,
what is it in German, then
Kabir table must be visible, you must be recognizing this mucus,
if we have seen our favorite
near episode, if you have not seen it, then
go and do
that concept, if this mix up gets
complicated then you can get it, if
you are near, then it is less
clear, then that and this table is SIM only,
when I have used it,
where that address was, only God was there,
God, rest everything is normal,
give this mix and for beer, for hair it
is the same, what is its reason and benefit,
you will see the required table properly, only for
this and two  It is irrefutable, different, the rest
is semi-
intelligent, so if you understand this best cable, then you have understood
what to use, you have understood
where to use it, let's see, okay, now
in the second part, what is the most
important, which is to
use it with which category, which replace you
with the year, the first part which is the
most important, 99% important, these
passwords are the first ones with which you should always
use them, so we call them triple x
new words, if that works then definitely
yes, you will use this form, so whatever
good qualities Aryan, whatever you see in grocery now, you will
see it with this, that means if it is Brian, then someone will
give these destroyers, if it is
interest year end, then this interest year will
give it, you also have to do the same, you will
learn this, so it is visible, this search center
Sureon is not visible, once aunty,
then we are using it, it is simple that
you
12 Prized S A Great British,
cleaning the records from your top table  If you use it,
you will find it easy that the wife is in the
fire and what he said and that Ram is going to
learn in the next class, don't worry,
and in a few episodes,
I am
waiting for Diwali, so how does that happen, this
problem with this period, you are seeing
two producers in the festival,
that he sees what will happen, hair oil ad Yash
and festival trusted in German, this interest
service, for example, then 2 inches you are interested
in German, two interest district wise who is interested,
entry service, sure, it
is simple, but you just have to remember that
interest rearrangement, which
comes with it, and
if you see the list of some categories that I have given you, you can see
on the side, there are some important
ones in it, sister means to do Hari, it is a big loss, there is
tumor, you just have to remember this
when you are learning, on which he is
Cambridge, learn these with restriction
and then you  I remember I have to cure it, so did you
not understand this disease, it is so simple when it
comes with it, it will match with it, right now
other
's powder is not used, you can understand something outside,
sometimes it may be effective,
sometimes it may not be, but for example, what is
my car,
this year the result is human on the simple side, I
sometimes take a bath in the river, you can say
I wash myself, this year we will also put this Vansh
Vriddhi Kunwar and Murder's policy
Muzaffarnagar
in your purse, logically that you
do it in it, so this year we will start and if I
accept you now, then
you will feel easy that look, right now I
wear clothes or I wear clothes, I will keep myself for the
first time, so
in German, this canal is about to break,
so what will happen, in this river example, I had to
dress myself, come on the dry dress message,
if you are wearing a sweater to yourself, then
who is the first one,
what are you saying, waiter devotees, the sweater is done,
you have to do it on the setting, from  If I am wearing it then
what happened to me, that is why there was
this vast media and full and on
that item in itself but confusing I
completely understand but you are using it, you will
not use it normally, even if you
do then do it logically that it is going to come, I had made it important for
myself that the
rule over protective vest is
important for you and it is a good thing that this
rule which is active from almost all of them with any where
presented and as we
saw the plate, it is the same, so there is
no need to worry about it,
Ramesh from the Dastaan ​​Beach Center, so I love keep mixing, do you
understand anything, so see if the acid,
as I said, right now in this entry
amateur Deutsch, where did the interest religious
come from, it seems illogical, but it is,
if the acid has to be kept a little on the magic side at some places, this is
impressing in German, so it is
yoga, just remember that that
Beyblade, so just revise the soil  It is
because of what we said earlier that the
mature in English was white, by the way this also
happens, so you saw the table for sending the message,
we said that brother this is the
table of this mixture, we made it a little easier because it is an
exam, so it is okay for the country,
then we saw that there are two types of words,
reflect, Shiv, a true, a parcel through, so
you will see the list again on the
help screen, so
you have to remember that you do not have to fry the rest, you do
not have to remember the problem,
and then when you use it, the
second scene on it is always walnut or pimple and some such
words, which ever tree
you use, then ginger is
important and flexible, I
hope you have understood this difference,
we will meet in the next episode, thank you.